luxeyard.com 2018-10-07

# Home Decor for Every Lifestyle | Privacy | LuxeYard

**We Respect Your Privacy and Will Protect Your Information**

**Last Updated April 21, 2015**

At LuxeYard.com, we believe you're entitled to decide what information you share with us and how it is used, so we answer your questions about privacy up front!

**1\. Why does LuxeYard.com collect visitor information?**

We gather information with three objectives in mind:

>   * To fulfill your order accurately and quickly.
> 
>   * To learn how we can improve your shopping experience.
> 
>   * To help us meet our commitment to privacy.
> 
> 

When you visit LuxeYard.com, you have the option of creating a LuxeYard.com user account, which is not required to place an online order from LuxeYard.com. However, LuxeYard.com user account also gives you free access to these valuable features:

>   * Save items to your Favorite Things.
> 
>   * Quicker and easier access to your order history.
> 
>   * Get access to special promotions.
> 
>   * View delivery details and lead times instantly.
> 
>   * Creating a user account is easy:
> 
>   * Enter your e-mail address and name.
> 
>   * Choose and confirm a password.
> 
> 

When you place an order, we will ask for additional information needed to fulfill your order:

>   * Your delivery address and phone.
> 
>   * Your billing address and phone.
> 
>   * Your credit card information.
> 
> 

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend's e-mail address. LuxeYard.com will automatically send the friend a one-time e-mail inviting them to visit the site. LuxeYard.com stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time e-mail and tracking the success of our referral program.

**2\. How does LuxeYard.com's web site remember me automatically?**

LuxeYard.com uses a technology called "cookies" to remember you and the information you are saving. When you visit our web site, we send you back a cookie, a small text file that includes a temporary inquiry number, your IP address, plus any items you've chosen. The information we store in cookies is also linked to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. Your web browser has a special folder on your computer where it keeps cookies. Cookies cannot harm your computer in any way. Only the website that places a cookie on your computer is allowed to read it; no other website may access the cookie LuxeYard.com's places on your computer. If you are visiting LuxeYard.com from a computer that only you or your family use, cookies present no security concern. However, if you are using a shared computer in a public environment (i.e. a library, work, coffee house), others using that computer to visit LuxeYard.com can log in as you. Although LuxeYard.com never displays your credit card information on our website, someone logging in as you could access less confidential data, such as your name or shipping address. If this applies to you, consider choosing not to be "remembered" when you register using a shared computer in a public environment. Instead, log in at each visit. Cookies make your shopping experience much easier. If you are trying to decide between two sofas, the cookie enables your computer to find those items again without doing a whole new search. Your browser looks in its cookie folder, finds your LuxeYard.com's cookie and tells LuxeYard.com that you want to look at the same sofas again. When you add an item to your Shopping Cart, request a price, or place an order, your cookie may hold information with the details of the items you're considering ordering. If you don't want any information stored in a cookie, you can set your browser not to accept cookies, but remember that cookies make your purchases easy. They enable your computer to keep a list of items you're considering or to place them directly in your Shopping Cart (so you don't have to re-enter them manually).

**3\. What visitor information does LuxeYard.com's web site keep track of?**

Information tracked automatically is generic and doesn't include any personal details: When you log onto the Internet, your computer says to your Internet service, "Here I am; talk to me!" by requesting an IP (Internet protocol) address, sort of like asking for a seat at an electronic table with numbered seats. Your Internet service's computer responds by saying, "OK, for this session, you sit at #12." Some providers assign you a permanent or "static" IP address, but most use temporary ones. This helps ensure your privacy, because it's difficult, if not impossible, to collect personal information about you via a temporary address. Our site keeps a general list of visitors' IP addresses. This gives us broad, generic information such as how many users from a specific ISP log onto LuxeYard.com's web site and helps us maintain compatibility with many different Internet services. LuxeYard.com records browser types and versions so we can answer questions such as, "How many of our visitors were using Netscape Communicator(r) 4.6 last month?" This tells us what features our visitors can make use of and helps us keep our website up to date. We record how many people visit each page on our site. This helps answer questions such as, "Which items or pages are drawing a lot of interest this month?" We may also record which site or search engine referred you to LuxeYard.com. This information enhances your shopping experience: images look better, pages load more quickly, and this site remains compatible with more browsers and systems. Information you enter when you register or place an order makes your shopping experience at LuxeYard.com easy. At any point while you're browsing, you can place an item in your Shopping Cart. When you're done browsing, you can review your Shopping Cart. If you want to place an order, indicate the item(s) you wish to order and click the Proceed to Checkout button. Enter your delivery information, including: name, address, and preferred contact time/method in case we need to get in touch with you about your order. The next screen gives you a price quote for the item(s) you're ordering, including price and applicable sales tax. The Purchase button then displays options for payment: You can enter credit card information here.

**4\. What does LuxeYard.com do with this information?**

LuxeYard.com has an absolute commitment to keep your information secure. The information you share with us is used to fulfill your order and to keep you up-to-date on the status of your order. After you place an order, we'll contact you with information about the order as needed. The financial institutions processing your payment or your financing application may send us supplemental information if there is a problem in completing the transaction. The retailer / shipper fulfilling your order may send us supplemental information if there is a problem with delivery. This information is used only in processing your order(s) from LuxeYard.com. Information about your browser helps us improve the way our site appears on your computer and makes sure our site is up to date and compatible with your system. Traffic reports (information about sites that refer visitors to us) help us select the best places to reach people interested in shopping for furniture online.

**5\. Does LuxeYard.com ever share such information? With whom?**

Your information is never shared with anyone, except in connection with your order. Credit card or check information is only shared with financial institutions that process your payment. Shipping information is shared with the retail partners that fulfill your order. Information on financing applications goes directly to the financial institution that handles the financing, not to LuxeYard.com; we never see your application information, only your approval code, name and address. Technically, this shared information does pass out of our direct control, but LuxeYard.com makes clear to financial companies and retail partners we work with that we expect your information to be handled in accordance with LuxeYard.com's Privacy Policy. We do not sell, rent, share, trade or give away any of the information you provide to us except to the financial institutions processing your payment or your financing application and the retailers / shippers that produce and/or deliver your order. No third party will solicit you as a result of information within our control. It is true that the information you provide is subject to disclosure pursuant to judicial or other government subpoenas, warrants, or orders. Other than these fairly extreme cases, your personal information will be shared with no one. Use the links on our Help page to contact us. In addition, you can write to us at [info@LuxeYard.com](mailto:info@LuxeYard.com) with comments or to ask for information about this privacy policy. Any e-mail you send us is kept confidential and will not be posted on our site without your written permission.

**6\. What types of emails will LuxeYard.com send to me? Can I choose not to receive these emails?**

As a registered LuxeYard.com user, you may occasionally receive emails from us, including:

Newsletters Special Offers

Should you no longer wish to receive these emails, you may "opt out" at any time by logging in to your LuxeYard.com Account and clicking "Update your email preferences." Alternatively, you may email us at [membercare@LuxeYard.com](mailto:membercare@LuxeYard.com) or you may mail your request to Windy City Promotions, LLC. 2400 E Main St, Suite 331, St. Charles, IL 60174. Attention: Privacy. When you place an order with LuxeYard.com, you will also receive email updates regarding the status of your order. These emails, which are critical to fulfilling your order, will not be affected by updating your email preferences.

**7\. Can I tell LuxeYard.com not to gather or keep track of my visit via the cookie?**

Yes. You can set your browser not to accept cookies, but remember that cookies make your purchases easy. They enable your computer to keep a list of items you're considering or to place them directly in your Shopping Cart (so you don't have to re-enter them manually).

**8\. How do I correct or update information about me and my order(s)?**

To change, correct, or update information about you or your order prior to shipment, please access the "My Account" area of our website. Alternatively, contact us at [membercare@LuxeYard.com](mailto:membercare@LuxeYard.com).

**9\. Can I have my name removed from LuxeYard.com's active records? How?**

If you would like your name removed from our active records, you may go to your Account and click "edit my e-mail preferences". Alternatively, you may also send an e-mail to [membercare@LuxeYard.com](mailto:membercare@LuxeYard.com).

**10\. How do I contact LuxeYard.com with any questions about this policy?**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact:

Privacy Policy Coordinator: Windy City Promotions, LLC. 2400 E Main St, Suite 331, St. Charles, IL 60174

**11\. How will I know if this policy has been changed?**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, or other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via e-mail. Secure Shopping We make certain that we never share the information you've shared with us. We also make sure that your information is protected as you send it to us. Our secure server software (SSL) is among the best technology available today. It encrypts (scrambles in code) all personal data you share with us, including your credit card and telephone numbers, name and address. LuxeYard.com is so confident in our systems that we ensure 100% safety in the transactions you make with us. In the rare event that unauthorized charges are made to your credit card during a transaction with us, you will not be held responsible in any way. Under federal law, your bank cannot hold you liable for more than $50 of fraudulent charges. If your bank does hold you liable for any of this $50, LuxeYard.com will cover the entire liability for you, up to the full $50. LuxeYard.com will cover this liability only if the unauthorized use of your credit card resulted through no fault of your own, on purchases made at LuxeYard.com while using the secure server. In the event of unauthorized use of your credit card, in order to qualify for the LuxeYard.com security guarantee, you must undertake any steps required by federal law and your credit card agreement, including any provision requiring you to notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures. If you have any questions regarding federal laws, contact your state's attorney general or the United States Department of the Treasury.
